VICTOR LOPES MOTA BACKEND DEVELOPER



About me

I am a software engineer graduated from the University of Brasilia, Brazil, I like to help my co-workers, I always try to have a good relationship with them and learn as much as I can. I interned for two years at the Federal Senate, and worked as a Junior Developer for a year and a half at Tata Consultancy Services. I am currently a Junior Developer at Sea Tecnologia.

Hard-skills

- Java / Kotlin
- MySQL
- Angular / React
- SonarQube
- Nexus
- Python / Python Django

• Git / GitHub / GitLab

- Soft-skills
- People and interpersonal skills
- · Self-awareness and self-learning
- Time management
- Emotional intelligence

Work Experience

Junior Developer - Sea Tecnologia

February 2023 - Current

- Implementation, maintenance of requested features. Perform pairing, functional code and with good development practices;
- The main technologies used were:
- - Java with JSP, Liferay Framework, Gitlab
- - Angular and React

Junior Backend Developer - TCS

Mar 2021 - July 2022

- Features development, testing, deployment in unit and integrated testing environments and production, and project maintenance when necessary.
- The main technologies used were:
- - Java, Java with Spring Boot, JSP, JSF, Maven, Kotlin, HTML5, CSS and JS
- - Angular

Internship - Senado Federal

Aug 2017 - Aug 2019

- Assistance in sectoral activities, management and monitoring of processes, as well as visual updates on the pages of the Federal Senate.
- The main technologies used were:
- - Java, JS, HTML, CSS, Liferay
- - Bizagi Modeler

Education

• Software Engineering - University of Brasilia

• English Exchange Course - Englishour - Dublin - Ireland

August 2013 - March 2021 July 2022 - December 2022

Certifications

• AWS Serverless REST APIs for Java Developers. CI/CD included

• FULL Java 2021: From Zero to Professional

• Android Development With Kotlin

Udemy - 15 hours Udemy - 77 hours Udemy - 28 hours